Zerad Henny Shopify Developer

zeradhenny474@gmail.com

+1 (970) 639 0991

• Chicago, IL, United States

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/zeradhenny-5a796a260/

PROFILE

Experience and results-oriented Shopify developer with excellent development skills and a bachelor's degree in Computer Science from the Hong Kong University of Science and Technology. Certified front-end developer with 7+ years of experience who is comfortable working with JavaScript, HTML/CSS, and responsive web design to deliver exceptional customer experience. I have proven experience in creating and designing Shopify stores using a free theme from scratch. Track record for ready graspring difficult concepts quickly and has proven leadership/ teamwork skills. Displays determination in all endeavours with attention to accuracy for optimal end results.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

September 2021 – November 2022 Orland Park, United States

Senior Shopify Developer

SQ2 Media, LLC

- Building landing pages and using Shopify APIs to improve UI/UX.
- Provide estimates of the required level of accuracy for stores.
- Development of sites and web applications with complex graphics.
- Shopify Template development from design XD/Zeplin/Figma at more than 10 stores.
- Technical support, solution finding, brainstorming.
- A/B Test setup through Google Optimizer.

March 2017 – August 2018 Brighton, Australia

Shopify Developer

Soft Solutions

- Build API-driven integration with various consumer marketing platforms.
- Test deliverables against a user's story's acceptance tests.
- Integrate with critical eCommerce systems, either developing new interfaces or modifying existing ones.
- Sincere passion to delight customers, solve problems and provide a positive experience.
- Shopify API integration at more than 10 stores
- Implement SEO Optimization | CRO.
- Development membership, event and legal platform technology solutions and automated interface code.

April 2016 – February 2017 Revesby, Australia

Junior Shopify Developer

Nemco

- Theme development & customization
- Shopify app integration
- Shopify store design and responsive design at more than 3 stores.
- Development Shopify stores from scratch more 5 stores.
- Shopify page speed optimization. Improve site speed from 24 to 78 at more than 4 stores.
- Development of sites and web applications with complex graphics.



Frontend

• • • • •

Backend

• • • •

HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Shopify, Shopify Plus, Shopify Development, Shopify Templates, Shopify Theme, eCommerce, jQuery Node.js, PHP, SEO

PROJECTS

https://shopwearmepro.com

- · Shopify theme development
- · Shopify theme customization
- SEO
- · Migrate sites from other CMS to Shopify.

https://shop.ontarioparks.com

- Shopify theme customization
- Shopify store design and responsive design
- Shopify app integration
- · Shopify speed optimization

https://www.leatherheadsports.com

- Theme customization
- SEO
- · Shopify API integration
- Page Speed Optimization
- Building Landing Page

EDUCATION

2011 - 2015 Bachelor/Computer science

Clear Water Bay, Hong Hong Kong University of Science and Technology

Kong, China